所以，既然你已经掌握了基础知识
So, now that you got the fundamentals
盒子模型下来，
of the box model down,
让我们更进一步，谈谈不同的类型
let's go one step further and talk about different types
盒子模型中存在的盒子数量。
of boxes that exist in the box model.
也许你已经注意到
And maybe you had already noticed
CSS中有不同类型的框。
that there are different types of boxes in CSS.
因此，让我们在这里检查这个元素以向您展示我的意思。
So let's inspect this element here to show you what I mean.
所以这个，例如，
So this one, for example,
你会看到这个 h2 元素占据了所有的空间
and you see that this h2 element occupies all the space
它可以占据，
that it can occupy,
所以基本上它从左边一直走
so basically it goes all the way from the left side
在右边，对吧？
to the right side, right?
同样如此，例如，对于整个标题，
And the same is true, for example, for this entire header,
当然，对于整篇文章和标题也是如此。
of course, for this entire article and the header as well.
而且真的大部分元素都是这样的，
And really most of the elements are like this,
但还有其他元素。
but then there are also other elements.
所以其他盒子可以这么说，比如这个。
So other boxes so to say, like this one.
所以这里我们有这个强大的元素，
So here we have this strong element,
但你看到它只占据了空间
but you see that it only occupies exactly the space
它的内容实际上在哪里。
where its content actually is.
同样的事情也是如此，例如，
And the same thing is true, for example,
对于这个图像在这里。
for this image here.
所以你会看到，它只有 50x50 像素，
So you'll see, it's only really 50x50 pixels,
这正是内容本身的大小。
which is exactly the size of the content itself.
例如，这里的锚标签也是一样的，
And for example, the same thing here with this anchor tag,
您现在将再次看到
which again you will now see
它恰好占据了宽度
that it occupies exactly the width
这是其内容所必需的。
that is needed for its content.
所以这些类型的盒子只占
So these types of boxes that only occupied
正是他们内容所需的空间
exactly the space that they need for its content
就是我们所说的内联框，
is what we call inline boxes,
另一方面，所有这些其他盒子。
and on the other hand, all these other boxes.
例如，这个段落，或者这个 h3 标题，
So for example, this paragraph, or this h3 heading,
这些我们称为块级框或块级元素。
these we call block-level boxes or block-level elements.
所以块级元素或框
So block-level elements or boxes
尽可能占据所有空间，
occupy all the space that they can,
他们基本上在他们之后创建换行符。
and they basically create line breaks after them.
或者换句话说，
Or in other words,
他们不能并排在一起，对吧？
they cannot be side-by-side with one another, right?
所以当然，
So of course,
如果他们横向占据了他们需要的所有空间，
if they take up all the space they need horizontally,
那么他们当然不能并排。
then of course they cannot be side-by-side.
这是有道理的，对吧？
That makes sense, right?
所以这些是根本的区别
So these are the fundamental differences
在块级框和行内框之间。
between block-level boxes and inline boxes.
但还有一些，
But there are some more,
所以让我们看一个比较。
so let's take a look at a comparison.
所以在这里我突出显示了所有的块级元素
So here I highlighted all of the block-level elements
或现在我们页面上的块级框。
or block-level boxes that are on our page right now.
正如我已经提到的，
And as I already mentioned,
这些元素基本上被格式化为块。
these elements are basically formatted as blocks.
这么大的内容块，
So big blocks of content,
它占据了父元素宽度的 100%。
which occupies 100% of the parent element's width.
即使内容本身也是如此
And that is true even if the content itself
实际上不需要那么多空间。
wouldn't actually require so much space.
例如，这个“什么是 HTML”标题，
For example, this "What is HTML" heading,
实际上它不需要整条线，对吧？
actually it wouldn't need the entire line, right?
但它仍然是块级元素
But it is still a block-level element
因为那样它们可以垂直堆叠
because then they can be stacked vertically
默认一个接一个。
one after another by default.
现在，有一件非常重要的事情要提
Now, one thing that is very important to mention
是盒子模型完全适用
is that the box model applies exactly
正如我之前向您展示的块级元素
as I showed you before to block-level elements
而对于内联元素，情况并非如此，
while the same is not true for inline elements,
我们马上就会看到。好的？
as we will see in a second. Okay?
现在默认情况下，大多数 HTML 元素
Now by default, most of the HTML elements
实际上是 b锁级元素，
are actually block-level elements,
所以像body、main、header这样的东西，
so things like the body, main, header,
等等等等。
and so on and so forth.
所以我们真正使用的大部分元素
So most of the elements really that we use
是块级元素，
are block-level elements,
所以我们也可以说他们创建了块级盒子。
so we can also say that they create block-level boxes.
好的。
All right.
现在，我们可以用 CSS 做的一件事
Now, one thing that we can do with CSS
就是从行内框变成块级框。
is to change from inline boxes to block-level boxes.
我们可以通过显示属性集来做到这一点
And we can do that with the display property set
块的值，
to the value of block,
但我们将在一秒钟内在实践中做到这一点。
but we will do that in practice in a second.
但是现在，我想做的
But for now, what I want to do
就是看内联元素
is to look at the inline element
以及它与块级元素的不同之处。
and how it's different from block-level elements.
所以在这里我用这个红色边框标记了内联元素，
So here I marked the inline elements with this red border,
你会看到如预期的那样，
and you see that as expected,
他们只占据了空间
they only occupied exactly the space
这是其内容所必需的。
that is needed for its content.
他们也不会在之后创建任何换行符
They also don't create any line breaks after
或在元素之前。
or before the element.
因此，他们可以简单地呆在里面
And so therefore they can simply stay inside
他们的父元素没有创建
of their parent elements without creating
任何额外的空间。
any additional space.
这正是对较小元素有意义的原因，
And this is exactly what makes sense for smaller elements,
比如强元素，em元素，
like the strong element, the em element,
或锚元素，对吧？
or anchor elements, right?
我们不希望这些元素创建一个新行
We wouldn't want these elements to create a new line
并尽可能占据所有宽度。
and occupy all the width that they can.
就是没有任何意义，
That just wouldn't make any sense,
这就是为什么我们有
and therefore that's why we have
这些不同类型的盒子。
these different types of boxes.
但无论如何，现在关于盒子模型，正如我所说，
But anyway, now about the box model, as I said,
它在内联元素中的工作方式不同。
it works differently in inline elements.
所以对于内联元素，
So for inline elements,
高度和宽度属性没有任何影响。
the height and width properties do not have any effect.
填充和边距也仅水平应用
Also paddings and margins are only applied horizontally
或者换句话说，在左侧和右侧，
or in other words, on the left and right sides,
但不在顶部和底部。
but not on the top and bottom.
而这个根本区别
And this fundamental difference
关于盒子模型如何适用于内陆元素
about how the box model works for inland elements
始终牢记这一点非常重要
is extremely important to always keep in mind
并且永远不会忘记，
and to never forget,
因为这是我看到初学者的错误
because this is a mistake that I see beginners
让所有的时间，
make all the times,
这基本上是不明白
which is basically do not understand
为什么盒子模型的某些属性不起作用
why certain properties of the box model do not work
正如预期的那样应用于内联元素。
as expected when applied to inline elements.
所以请注意这一点，因为它非常重要
So take note of this as it is very important
要始终牢记。
to always keep in mind.
现在默认情况下，
Now by default,
一些是内联元素的元素，
some of the elements that are inline elements,
所以创建内联框的是锚点，图像，
so which create inline boxes are the anchor, image,
strong、em、按钮以及更多。
strong, em, the button as well, and many more.
现在，就像我们可以用来显示属性一样
Now, just like we can use to display property
使任何元素成为块级元素，
to make any element a block-level element,
我们也可以使用显示设置为内联
we can also use display set to inline
为了转换任何块级元素
in order to transform any block-level element
到内联元素。
to an inline element.
实际上现在让我们回到我们的代码
And actually let's now go back to our code
看看其中一些事情的实际效果。
to see some of these things in action.
让我们首先尝试在此处格式化这些链接
And let's start by trying to format these links here
在标题中。
that are in the header.
所以让我们选择它们，但我会做得更多。
So let's select them, but I will do that more down.
让我在这里创建一些评论。
Let me actually create some comments here.
所以让我们说这些就像页面部分
So let's say that these are like page sections
或类似的东西。
or something like that.
所以基本上我们页面的所有大的分割部分。
So basically all the big dividing pieces of our page.
所以我们当然有身体，
So we have the body, of course,
容器，主标题，
the container, the main header,
导航、文章和所有这些。
the navigation, article, and all of that.
然后这里是我们开始的地方，
And then here is where we start to have,
或喜欢较小的元素。
or like smaller elements.
这里的这些标题并不重要。
And these titles here don't really matter.
我只想拥有像视觉上的分离
I just want to have like a visual separation
代码里面。
inside of the code.
好的，让我们一路向下。
Okay, so let's go down here all the way down.
也许让我们看看这里。
Maybe let's see here.
所以我想选择所有的链接
And so I want to select all the links
在导航里面。
that are inside of the navigation.
所以让我们说导航，然后是那里的链接。
So let's say navigation and then the links in there.
和往常一样，
And as always,
我应该使用链接伪类来实际设置它们的样式。
I should use the link pseudo class to actually style them.
现在为了更好地了解这一点，会发生什么，
Now to see this a little bit better, what happens,
让我们给他们一种颜色，一种背景颜色，
let's give them a color, a background color,
像橙红色，现在我需要在这里手动重新加载。
like orange red, and now I need to manually reload here.
好的，所以我们得到了背景颜色
Okay, so we got that background color
现在让我们开始在这里添加一些边距，
and now let's start by adding some margin here,
就这样我们看到盒子模型实际上是这样的，
just so we see that the box model does in fact,
没有像我们想象的那样应用。
not applied way that we thought it would.
所以让我们说20像素并给它一个保存。
So let's say 20 pixels and give it a save.
您会看到一些边距被水平编辑。
And you see that some margin was edit horizontally.
所以在左边和右边，右边。
So on the left and right side, right.
但没有发生的是垂直空间被创造出来。
But what did not happen was that vertical space was created.
所以顶部和底部边距保持不变。
So the top and bottom margins remained unchanged.
现在，如果我们在盒子模型中检查一下，
Now, if we check this out here in the box model,
在开发工具中，它仍然会出现在这里，
in the dev tools, then it will still appear down here,
这里还有一些空间。
some more space here.
所以你会看到 20 的值仍然出现，
So you see that the 20 value does still appear,
但是在彩色覆盖层上，
but then here on the colored overlay,
所以这里这个橘子，其实并没有创造任何空间，
so here this orange, actually did not create any space,
尽管这里说的是 20，对吧？
even though it says 20 here, right?
所以，正如你现在所知道的，
And so, as you know by now,
原因是锚元素
the reason for that is that the anchor element
是一个内联元素，其中盒子模型
is an inline element where the box model
不创造任何垂直空间，
does not create any vertical space,
填充也是如此。
and the same is true for padding.
所以填充20像素。
So padding of 20 pixels.
那么让我们看看。
So let's see.
现在它确实看起来好像创造了一些空间，
And now it does actually look as if some space was created,
但这仅适用于元素内部
but that is only true for inside of the element
因为其实主播内容，
because in fact, the anchor content,
所以锚内容本身还是
so the anchor content itself is still
在完全相同的地方，
in the exact same place,
但如果这是一个块级元素，
but if this was a block-level element,
那么所有这些都会下降一点。
then all of this would have moved down a little bit.
所以基本上这个元素的填充区域
So basically the fill area of this element
已扩展并填充了背景颜色，
has been expanded and filled with the background color,
但实际上并没有创造新的空间。
but no new space was in fact created.
好的？
Okay?
但如果我们真的想拥有那个空间，
But if we actually want to have that space,
如果我们希望元素一个接一个，
and if we want the elements to be one after another,
那么我们当然可以将它们更改为块级元素。
then of course we can change them to block-level elements.
这正是我在幻灯片中向您展示的内容
So that is exactly what I showed you in the slide
通过使用显示属性
by using the display property
并将其设置为块的值。
and set it to the value of block.
所以这将渲染内联元素
So this will then render the inline element
作为块级元素。
as a block-level element.
那么你认为会发生什么
So what do you think will happen
一旦我现在保存这个？
once I save this now?
我们走了，
And there we go,
现在所有这些元素都占据了它们可以占据的所有宽度
now all of these elements occupy all the width that they can
他们现在实际上也有
and also they have now actually
它们之间的垂直边距也是如此。
also vertical margins between them.
现在它们有点在这个标题元素之外现在
Now they are kind of outside of this header element now
因为我们将标题元素设置为固定高度，
because we set the header element to a fixed height,
所以在之前的一堂课中。
so in one of the previous lectures.
因此，让我通过叠加层向您展示这一点。
So let me show that to you with the overlay.
我们这里需要更多的空间。
We need some more space here.
因此，由于我们将高度设置为标题
And so since we set the height to the header
到 80 像素的特定值，
to a specific value of 80 pixels,
然后内容不再适合那里，
then the content no longer fits in there,
所以元素没有展开
and so the element did not expand
为了适应内容。
in order to fit the content.
所以这就是为什么通常
So that's the reason why usually
我们没有在元素上设置固定高度。
we don't set a fixed height on elements.
所以让我回去改变它，
So let me go back and change that,
所以这只是一个演示。
so that was just a demo anyway.
所以是的，这是我们设置为 80 的高度。
So yeah, here is the height that we set to 80.
所以让我评论一下，再次保存。
So let me comment that out, save it again.
现在元素在这里垂直扩展
Now the element expanded vertically here
考虑到所需的额外空间。
to account for the additional space that is required.
好的。所以希望这是有道理的。
Okay. So hopefully that makes sense.
但这里的重点是这里的这些锚元素
But the main point here is that these anchor elements here
现在满足所有条件
now do satisfy all the conditions
作为块级元素。
of being a block-level element.
所以盒子模型通常适用于它们，
So the box model applies to them normally,
它们占据了可用宽度的 100%，
and they occupy 100% of the available width,
因此它们一个接一个地出现
and so therefore they appear one after another
很好地格式化为块。
nicely formatted as blocks.
好的。
All right.
所以它们占据了我们在这里看到的所有空间，
So they occupy all the space as we see here,
这当然包括边距。
which of course includes the margin.
因此，如果我们看一下，这些中的每一个都有一些余量，对吗？
So each of these, if we take a look has some margin, right?
这就是这里的橙色。
So that is this kind of orange color here.
所以这是整个空间的一部分
And so that is part of the entire space
元素本身需要，好吗？
that the element itself requires, all right?
好吧，让我们回到这里
Well, let's go back down here
实际上把这一切都关掉
and actually turn all of this off
因为这实际上只是一个演示。
because this was really just a demo.
好的？而现在，当然，
Okay? And now of course,
我们将看到标题缩回
we will see the header shrink back
只在此处垂直占据它需要的空间。
to only occupy vertically here the space that it needs.
好吧，随着我们不断添加越来越多的元素，
All right, so as we keep adding more and more elements,
那么这应该增长，
then this should grow,
这正是之前发生的事情
which is exactly what's happened before
当这些链接更大时，
when these links were bigger,
但现在他们又变小了
but now they're back to being small
因此，不需要我们拥有的所有空间。
and therefore all that space we had was not required.
现在接下来，让我们快速尝试相反的方法
And now next, let's actually quickly try the opposite
并将一些块级元素更改为内联元素。
and change some block-level elements to inline elements.
例如，
So for example,
让我们试试会发生什么
let's try what happens
当我们将列表元素设为内联时。
when we make the list elements as inline.
显示，内联。
Display, inline.
让我们实际删除它。
Let's remove this actually.
现在你会看到这三个元素
And now you'll see that these three elements
现在基本上是并排的
are now basically side-by-side
并且只占用他们需要的空间。
and occupy only the space that they need.
实际上让我们把它带回来
And actually let's bring this back
因为正如我提到的，
because as I mentioned,
开发工具真的很重要
the dev tools are really so important
特别是像这些盒子一样叠加，对吧？
especially for overlaying like these boxes, right?
所以现在盒子像这样并排
So now the boxes are side-by-side like this
因为它们是内联框。
because they are inline boxes.
所以他们不再在他们之后创建换行符
So they no longer create the line breaks after them
并且只占用了他们需要的空间。
and only occupied a space that they need.
让我们尝试同样的方法。
Let's try the same.
我会在这里关闭它并在段落上尝试相同的操作。
I'll turn it off here and try the same on the paragraphs.
所以这看起来更奇怪
And so that looks even stranger
因为所有的文字基本上都塌了
because all the texts basically collapsed
只是变成一大行文字，看起来，对吧？
just into one big line of text, it looks like, right?
小号o 再次，现在这些元素中的每一个
So again, each of these elements now
基本上只占用它需要的空间。
basically only occupies the space that it needs.
好吧，但让我们删除它
All right, but let's remove this
因为在这种情况下没有多大意义，
because it doesn't make much sense in the situation,
但在某些情况下，它实际上很有意义。
but at some situations it actually makes a lot of sense.
现在，在很多情况下，
Now, in many situations,
更有意义的是转变
what makes even more sense is to transform
将块级元素转换为称为
a block-level element into something called
一个内联块元素。
an inline-block element.
所以基本上这是内联和块级的混合。
So basically that's a mix of inline and block-level.
因此，让我们快速检查一下这意味着什么。
So let's quickly check out what that means.
所以在这里，我们有一个块级的快速总结
So here, we have a quick summary of both the block-level
和内联框。
and the inline boxes.
所以我们已经知道，
So we already know that,
所以我们不需要再重复一遍。
so we don't need to go over all that again.
但是基本上还有第三种类型的盒子，
But then there's basically a third type of box,
这是这两者之间的混合。
which is a mix between these two.
正如我之前所说，这就是内联块框。
And so that is, as I said before, the inline-block box.
所以内联块框，
So inline-block boxes,
它们从外面看起来像内联，
they look like inlines from the outside,
但它们在内部表现得像块级元素。
but they behave like block-level elements on the inside.
所以这意味着内联块框
So what that means is that inline-block boxes
只占用内容所需的空间，
do only occupied the space that they need for the content,
因此它们不会导致任何换行符。
and so therefore they do not cause any line breaks.
所以这就是我所说的内联块框的意思
So this is what I mean when I say that the inline-block box
从外部看，它的行为就像一个内联框。
behaves like an inline box from the outside.
然而，正如我所说，
However, as I said,
它在内部表现得像一个块级盒子，
it behaves like a block-level box on the inside,
所以这意味着盒子模型适用
and so what that means is that the box model applies
就像它对块级框所做的那样。
just as it does for block-level boxes.
所以我们仍然可以设置高度和宽度，
00:16:29,130​​ --> 00:16:32,290
我们仍然可以使用边距和填充
So we can still set heights and width,
and we can still use margins and paddings
就像在块级盒子或块级元素上一样。
just like on block-level boxes or on block-level elements.
所以这些是一样的，
So these are kind of the same,
所以我一直交替使用它们。
so I keep using them interchangeably.
所以本质上，内联块框真的结合了
So essentially, inline-block boxes really combines
块级和内联两全其美。
the best of both worlds of block-level and inline.
为了创建一个 inline-block 元素，
And in order to create an inline-block element,
我们所要做的就是设置显示属性
all we have to do is to set the display property
到内联块，就是这样。
to inline-block and that's it.
现在让我们看看我们如何在实践中做到这一点
And so let's now see how we do that in practice
在某些情况下，这可能非常有用。
and some situations where this can be extremely helpful.
所以让我们回到我们的标题链接。
So let's go back here to our header links.
所以对于这个导航，
So to this navigation,
这样我就可以告诉你一个 inline-block 元素在哪里
so that I can show you where an inline-block element
会很有帮助。
can be very helpful.
所以现在这里还有很多格式，
So right now there is another lot of formatting here,
就像没有间距一样，所以我们需要解决这个问题。
so like no spacing, so we need to fix that.
所以这是在下面的某个地方，就在这里。
So this was somewhere down here, right here.
所以让我们回到尝试添加一些边距
And so let's go back to trying to add some margins
暂时不更改显示属性中的任何内容。
without changing anything in the display property for now.
假设我们想要 30 像素的边距，
So let's say we wanted a margin of 30 pixels,
这应该可行，因为这是一个水平空间，
and this should work because this is a horizontal space,
所以这甚至适用于内联元素。
and so that works even on inline elements.
但是现在如果我想添加一个边距顶部
But now if I wanted to add a margin top
比方说 10 个像素，那么什么都不会改变，对吧？
of let's say 10 pixels, then nothing will change, right?
所以它保持不变，这正是行为
So it's stays the same and that's exactly the behavior
我们一开始就已经看到了。
that we saw already at the beginning.
但是现在如果我们将显示改为 inline-block，
But now if we change the display to inline-block,
然后看看会发生什么。
then see what happens.
所以你看到了，现在我们在这里得到了我们的空间。
So you saw that now we got our space here.
如果我们检查一下，
And if we check this out,
那么您确实可以看到右侧的橙色空间
then indeed you can see that orange space on the right side
然后是 th 上的 10 个像素e 顶部。
and then the 10 pixels on the top.
所以盒子模型又被应用了
So the box model is back to being applied
作为块级元素，
as a block-level element,
但在外面，元素仍然是并排的
but on the outside the elements are still side-by-side
只占用他们需要的空间，
and occupying only the space they need,
所以表现得像内联元素。
so behaving like inline elements.
所以在某些情况下这是一个很棒的技术，
So this is a great technique in some situations,
即使在这一点上，
even though at this point,
我们也有更现代的方式来做类似的事情，
we also have more modern ways of doing something similar,
但在某些情况下，这实际上会很好知道，
but in some cases this will actually be very good to know,
以及工具带中的一项好技术。
and a good technique to have in your tool belt.
现在只是最后一个细节
Now just one final detail
是我们应该删除那个边距吗
is that we should remove that margin right
从最后一个元素开始。
from the last element.
所以让我们选择那个
So let's select that
导航链接，
nav a link,
现在你会看到一些新的东西。
and now you will see something new.
所以这里是一个伪类，对吧。
So this here is a pseudo class, right.
但在此之上，我们可以链接另一个伪类
But on to that we can chain another pseudo class
因为现在我们想要最后一个孩子，对吧。
because now we want the last-child, right.
像这样，然后我们要设置边距
Like this, and then we want to set the margin
直接归零就好了
right back to zero, okay.
所以在视觉上什么都没有改变，
So visually that changes nothing,
但是在这里我们现在看到这个不再有死空间
but here we now see that this one no longer has dead space
在右侧，很多时候这很重要。
on the right side and many times that's important to do.
所以这就是为什么我想告诉你我们可以连锁
And so that's why I wanted to show you that we can chain
这些到像这样的伪类没有任何问题。
these to pseudo classes like this without any problem.
太好了，现在要结束了，
Great, and now just to finish,
我想向你展示这些图像
I wanted to show you that images
实际上是内联块框。
are actually inline-block boxes.
好的。
All right.
所以我一开始就说图像
So I said in the beginning that images
实际上是内联元素，但实际上，
are actually inline elements, but in fact,
它们的行为确实像 inline-block 元素
they do behave like inline-block elements
我们可以很容易地通过添加一些边距来证明这一点，
and we can easily demonstrate this by adding some margin,
例如，这里的帖子图片。
for example, to this post image here.
因此，如果我在这里添加 100 像素的边距，
So if I add a margin of a 100 pixels here,
那么如果它是一个内联元素，
then if it was an inline element,
它不应该创建任何垂直空间。
it should not create any vertical space.
所以不在这里也不在这里。好的。
So not here and not here. All right.
但是请注意我保存它时会发生什么。
But watch what happens as I save this.
所以你确实看到了
And so indeed you see
这里所有的垂直空间都被添加了。
that all of this vertical space here was added.
所以这证明确实
And so that is proof that indeed
它是一个内联块元素
it is an inline-block element
事实也是如此
and the same is true for the fact
我们可以为这个元素设置宽度和高度。
that we can set width and heights for this element.
所以如果它是一个纯粹的内联元素，
So if it was a purely inline element,
那么这里的这两个也不行，对吧。
then these two here would also not work, right.
所以这也很重要
So that's also important to note
让我们在这里恢复正常。
and let's just set it back to normal here.
好的。这就是 CSS 中框的类型。
Okay. So that's it for the type of boxes in CSS.
就像一个快速的总结
Just as a quick summary
或者基本上作为这次讲座的收获，
or basically as a takeaway from this lecture,
大多数时候我们实际上会离开
most of the time we will actually leave
单独的显示设置
the display setting alone
并且只需使用预定义的框类型
and simply use the predefined box type
因为默认情况下，它们确实很有意义。
because by default, they do actually make a lot of sense.
但是，我们可以使用显示设置来阻止
However, we can use display set to block
为了制作一个小的内联元素，
in order to make a small inline element,
例如，占据一整行，
for example, occupy an entire line,
这是我们有时需要的东西
which is something that we will sometimes need
在现实世界。
in the real world.
然后反过来，
Then the other way around,
有时我们不想要块级元素
sometimes we don't want a block-level element
将所有其他元素推入新行。
to push all the other elements into a new line.
所以基本上我们并不总是希望他们占据
So basically we don't always want them to occupy
所有可用的空白空间填充。
all the available blank space that there is to fill.
所以在那种情况下，
And so in that case,
我们可以将它们设置为内联元素
we can set them to an inline element
或者可能更有用，
or probably even more useful,
我们可以将它们设置为 inline-block 元素
we can set them to an inline-block element
因为这样我们仍然可以像往常一样应用盒子模型。
because then we can still apply the box model as usual.